

# SU MYINT MYAT MOE

Designer/Illustrator

- sumyintmyatmoe@gmail.com
- (65) 8122 9576
- http://misakimoe.design

I have deep passion for creating beautiful and usable design and user interfaces. The foucs of my craft is visual deisgn, UI/UX, prototyping, usability testing. I have experiences with drawing vector illustrations and frontend coding. I am attentive to feedback, communicative and curious about the experiences that delight society.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelance Illustrator

January 2016 - Present

Work on vector illustrations.
Logo design of Rangoon Mapper.

#### UI/UX designer, Escape Pixel Co.Ltd

January 2016 - March 2017 (1 year and 3 months)

- Produced wireframes, mockups, prototypes, and design specifications.
- Designed logos, brand Identities, posters, infographic and visual assets.
- Conceptualized and designed websites based on client's requests.
- Shaped and conceptualized the product ideas of the clients by researching, wireframing and producing rapid prototypes.

#### Programmer, AcePlus Solutions Co.Ltd

April 2014 - December 2015 (1 year and 9 months)

- Worked along with the team for japanese offshore projects.
- Worked on mobile project for DCJ (defined Contribution Plan Consulting of Japan).
- Involved in development and maintenance of online meeting room reservation system
- Involved in testing, troubleshooting, resolved problems and produced documents.

#### Programmer (intern), ACE Data Systems

January 2014 - March 2014 (3 months)

- Involved in development of web-based application in ASP.NET using C#, SQL Server 2008 R2.
- Designed interface using HTML, ASP Tag, CSS, Javascript.

## **EDUCATION**

# University of Computer Studies, Yangon

2008 - 2012

Bachelor of Computer Science (B.C.Sc), Computer Science, Graduated with Honours

#### **SKILLS**

Wireframing

Prototyping

Graphic Design

Branding

Illustration

Front-end development

Tools

Photoshop

Illustrator

SketchApp

Invision and Marvel

Principle

Development

HTML/CSS

Javascript & JQuery

Java, C#

MySQL, MSSQL

### **LANGUAGE**

Myanmar

English

Japanese